http://www.globaldialysis.com/privacy.html

Empowering dialysis users and caregivers
Search for dialysis centres here
Log in to explore the world's most comprehensive database of dialysis centres for
free!
Jobs in dialysis
Professional dialysis recruitment
Privacy statement
Global Dialysis is committed to protecting your privacy
and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe
online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the Global
Dialysis Web site and governs data collection and usage. By using the
Global Dialysis website, you consent to the data practices described in
this statement.
Collection of your personal information
Global Dialysis collects personally identifiable
information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or
telephone number. Global Dialysis also collects anonymous demographic
information, which is not unique to you, such as your post code, age,
gender, preferences, interests and favourites.
There is also information about your computer hardware and
software that is automatically collected by Global Dialysis. This
information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names,
access times and referring web site addresses. This information is used
by Global Dialysis for the operation of the service, to maintain quality
of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the
Global Dialysis web site.
Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose
personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through
Global Dialysis public message boards, this information may be
collected and used by others. Note: Global Dialysis does not read any of
your private online communications.
Global Dialysis encourages you to review the privacy
statements of Web sites you choose to link to from Global Dialysis so
that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your
information. Global Dialysis is not responsible for the privacy
statements or other content on web sites outside of the Global Dialysis
and Global Dialysis family of web sites.
Use of your personal information
Global Dialysis collects and uses your personal
information to operate the Global Dialysis web site and deliver the
services you have requested. Global Dialysis also uses your personally
identifiable information to inform you of other products or services
available from Global Dialysis and its affiliates. Global Dialysis may
also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of
current services or of potential new services that may be offered.
Global Dialysis does not sell, rent or lease its customer
lists to third parties. Global Dialysis may, from time to time, contact
you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering
that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally
identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is
not transferred to the third party. In addition, Global Dialysis may
share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical
analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or
arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using
your personal information except to provide these services to Global
Dialysis, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your
information.
Global Dialysis does not use or disclose sensitive
personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations,
without your explicit consent.
Global Dialysis keeps track of the web sites and pages
our customers visit within Global Dialysis, in order to determine what
Global Dialysis services are the most popular. This data is used to
deliver customized content and advertising within Global Dialysis to
customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a
particular subject area.
Global Dialysis Web sites will disclose your personal
information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the
good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the
edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Global Dialysis
or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Global
Dialysis; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the
personal safety of users of Global Dialysis, or the public.
Use of Cookies
The Global Dialysis web site use "cookies" to help you
personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is
placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to
run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely
assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that
issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a
convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell
the web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example,
if you personalize Global Dialysis pages, or register with Global
Dialysis site or services, a cookie helps Global Dialysis to recall your
specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process
of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses,
shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Global
Dialysis web site, the information you previously provided can be
retrieved, so you can easily use the Global Dialysis features that you
customized.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify
your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to
decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive
features of the Global Dialysis services or Web sites you visit.
Security of your personal information
Global Dialysis secures your personal information from
unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Global Dialysis secures the
personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a
controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use
or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number)
is transmitted to other web sites, it is protected through the use of
encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.
Changes to this Statement
Global Dialysis will occasionally update this Statement
of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Global Dialysis
encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of
how Global Dialysis is protecting your information.
Contact information
Global Dialysis welcomes your comments regarding this
Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Global Dialysis has not
adhered to this Statement, please contact Global Dialysis at
This e-mail address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it
This e-mail address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it . We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
Share |
Dialysis travel
Search for dialysis centresUsing Global DialysisHoliday ideasYour storiesYour hints and tipsPhrase cardsDialysis travel insuranceHoliday dialysis in CroatiaHoliday dialysis in GreeceMauritius holiday dialysisHoliday dialysis in MexicoHoliday dialysis in ScotlandDialysis holidays in TurkeyDialysis travel for American citizens
Dialysis information
Books for dialysis usersDialysis eventsDialysis glossaryDialysis world newsDiet and nutritionDrugs used in renal careJournals and publicationsKidney bloggers' librarySustainable, green nephrologyTypes of dialysisLINKS
Global Dialysis
Contact usOur storyAims and objectivesAdvertiseVacanciesTerms of usePrivacyGlobal Dialysis newsSubscribe to RSS feedsUnsubscribe from our newsletter
HomeDIALYSIS CENTRE SEARCHInsurancesFor dialysis users /
carersUser guide for dialysis usersReview dialysis centresDialysis user information resourcesBook storeFor dialysis centresUser guide for
centre managersAdd
a dialysis centreBecome a Global Dialysis member5 Star Members ClubRecruitmentDialysis industry business servicesDialysis informationChronic kidney diseaseTypes of dialysisDialysis glossaryDiet and nutritionDrugs used in renal careCosts of dialysisTravel adviceDialysis travel insuranceHints and tipsYour storiesDialysis book shopAbout dialysis for dialysis usersRecipees and cookeryDialysis nursingAbout Global DialysisOur storyAims and objectivesAdvertise with usNewsGlobal Dialysis newsDialysis world
newsBlogsKamal's blogBig D and MeSteve's BlogDownloads and FREE stuff
Forgot login?
Register
Share
Resources
Notice:
Undefined index: URL in /home/globaldi/public_html/modules/mod_textlinkads/tmpl/default.php on line 153
Zoom Filings
REKZE Laboratories
Copyright © 2020 Global Dialysis. All Rights Reserved.
